digitaldjtips.com 2017-12-13

# Privacy Policy / Terms & Conditions - Digital DJ Tips

## 1\. Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

• To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

• To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

• To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

• To process transactions  
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Your consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [online privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. This policy was last modified on 26 Jan 2017.

**Contacting us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us via info AT digitaldjtips DOT com.

## 2\. Terms & Conditions

**Acceptance of terms**

By accessing, downloading, installing, or using the Digital DJ Tips Services, whether or not you become a registered user (“User”, “You”, “Yourself”, “Your”), You agree to be bound by these Terms, which You acknowledge that You have read and understood.

We reserve the right, at Our sole discretion, to change, modify or otherwise alter these Terms at any time. You must review these Terms at http://www.digitaldjtips.com/privacy-policy/ on a regular basis to keep Yourself informed of any changes.

**Earnings Disclaimer**  
Digital DJ Holdings Ltd (“Digital DJ Tips”) can not and does not make any guarantees about your ability to get results or earn any money with our ideas, information, tools, or strategies. What we can guarantee is your satisfaction with our paid-for training. We give you a 12-month 100% satisfaction guarantee on the products we sell subject to the terms below, so if you are not happy for any reason with the quality of our training you simply email us to request a refund. You should know that all products and services by our company are for educational and informational purposes only. Nothing on this page, any of our websites, sales pages or any of our content or curriculum is a promise or guarantee of results or future earnings, and we do not offer any legal, medical, tax or other professional advice. Any financial numbers referenced here, or on any of our sites or pages, are illustrative of concepts only and should not be considered average earnings, exact earnings, or promises for actual or future performance. Use caution and always consult your accountant, lawyer or professional advisor before acting on this or any information related to a lifestyle change or your business or finances. You alone are responsible and accountable for your decisions, actions and results in life, and by your registration here you agree not to attempt to hold us liable for your decisions, actions or results, at any time, under any circumstance.

**Refund Policy: Non-Subscription Digital Products**

You have 12 months from the date of the original purchase to request a refund for any non-subscription Digital DJ Tips product. Any refund request after the time limit will not be processed. Refunds can only be processed back to the card or PayPal account used to make the purchase initially. All prices are charged in US dollars, and all refunds will also be processed in US dollars. If you have purchased using a different currency we do not guarantee that your refund amount will be exactly the same as that amount you paid. This is due to currency exchange fluctuations and local bank charges outside of our control.

**Refund Policy: Subscription Digital Products**

Your Digital DJ Lab membership, which may start with a trial period, will continue month-to-month unless and until you cancel your membership or we terminate it. You must have internet access and provide us with a current, valid, accepted method of payment to use the service. We will bill the monthly membership fee to the payment method used when signing up unless updated or changed by subscriber. If you want to cancel, you must do so before it renews each month in order to avoid billing of the next month’s membership fees to your payment method.

_Refund Policy: Trial Subscriptions:_ Your membership may start with a discounted trial period. The trial period of your membership lasts for 30 days, or as otherwise specified during sign-up. Trials are for new and certain former members only. Digital DJ Holdings Ltd reserves the right, in its absolute discretion, to determine your trial eligibility. If you cancel your trial within the first 30 days you will receive a full refund for any amount paid.

_Refund Policy: Monthly Subscriptions:_ You have 30 days from the date of the the last payment to request a refund for your monthly subscription. Any refund request after the time limit will not be processed. You may cancel at any time. Only the last month’s subscription payment will be refunded.

_Refund Policy: Yearly Subscriptions:_ For yearly subscription purchases, you have THIRTY (30) Days from the date of the original purchase to request a refund for your Digital DJ Tips yearly subscription. Any refunds requests after 30 days will be prorated by the amount of time remaining under the original yearly subscription period. Example: If you purchase a yearly subscription in January of this year and you decide you want a refund 6 months from the purchase date, youre prorated refund would be 50% of the purchase price.

**EU VAT**  
All our prices are published in US Dollars, and do not include any applicable tax. By law, we are required to charge VAT at the local country rate to any purchases that are made in any one of the EU member states. This tax is added at the checkout and is clearly stated before the purchase process is completed. You can read more about these rules [here](https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/vat-supplying-digital-services-to-private-consumers/vat-businesses-supplying-digital-services-to-private-consumers).

**Your Account**

You agree to provide accurate and complete information when you register with, and as you use, the Digital DJ Tips Services, and you agree to update your account information to keep it accurate and complete. You agree that we may store and use the information you provide for use in maintaining and billing fees to your Account.
